A Guide to the Zelma Wilson Architectural Collection, 1940-1995
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- SERIES III: Project Records, 1956-1994 (Bulk 1969-1990) (Box 1-21, Oversize Map-case 25/Drawer 2, Oversize Map-case 21/Drawers 2-5, Box 25-218)
  - Higby, John and Arvella/Parcel 30 in Ojai Redevelopment Area formally known as Village Florist (Ojai, CA, 1986 Commercial) :[Ms]
  - Hill, Frank/Hill residence(Ojai, CA, 1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Hitching Post Estates/Hitching Post Estates Roof Repair(Ojai, CA, 1982 Residence):[Ms]
  - Hochman, Martin/Canine Enterprises (Ojai,CA, 1981-1982 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Holmes, Burt /Holmes residence(Ojai,CA,1976 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Horton, Mrs./Horton Remodel(Ojai, CA,1990 Residence):[Ms]
  - Hospitaller Order of St. John of God of Ojai, California, Inc./ Villa Granada, St. Joseph 's Residential Care Facility (Ojai,CA,1973-1978):[Ms,Dr]
  - Hultgen, Richard/Help-U-Sell signage (Ojai,CA,1988 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Humane Society of Ventura Co./Humane Society Addition (Ojai,CA,1978-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Hunter, Dr. and Mrs. James/Hunter residence (Saticoy, CA,1977-1984 Residence):[Ms]
  - Jackman, Royal and Elizabeth/Jackman residence(Ojai, CA,1973-1974 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Jackson, William E./Proposed apartment buildings (Mesa, AZ,1969 Residence):[Ms]
  - Jauregui, Robin and Michael/Jauregui Residence(Ojai ,CA,1969 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Jensen, Mr. and Mrs. Douglas /Jensen residence(Camarillo, CA, 1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Johnston, John/Johnston residence(Ojai, CA, 1979 Residence):[Ms]
  - Jones, Mary and Eve/ residence proposal(Santa Barbara,CA, 1990 Residence):[Ms]
  - Jones, Sally/Jones residence(Ojai, CA,1988 Residence):[Ms]
  - Jonker, Wim and Beth/Mira Monte Center (Mira Monte,CA,1985-1991 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - K&K Partnership AKA (William Kendall and Bob Moore)/Cloudbank Industrial (Ventura,CA,1986-1988 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Kane, Byron, Chairman Pethrus School for Exceptional Children/Pethrus School for Exceptional Children (Ojai, CA,1973-1974 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - KCPB, Inc./proposed transmitter(Thousand Oaks, CA,1979 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Keeler, Fred E. /Attitude Adjustment Shoppe, Ojai Shopping Center(Ojai,CA,1973-1975 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Keeler, Fred E./Maricopa West (Ojai,CA,1977-1980 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Keeler, Fred E./Sears remodel(CA, 1984 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Keeler, Fred E./Vallerio Plaza (Ojai, CA, 1982-1984 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Kelley, Narcissa/Kelley residence, remodel (CA, 1992 Residence):[Ms]
  - Ken O'Brien & Associates/Channel Islands Harbor, Phase III (Oxnard, CA, 1981-1985 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Kitley, Valera/Kitley building, Matilija Plaza ( Ojai, CA, 1976-1980 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Komorowski, Dick/Komorowski residence (Ventura, CA, 1984 Residence):[Ms]
  - Komura, Dr. Robert and Kip/Komura residence (Ojai, CA, 1988 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Kraus, Edward/ Santa Paula Super Market(Santa Paula, CA, 1961; 1967-1968 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Krishnamurti Foundation of America/Adult Education Center (Ojai, CA, 1983 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Krishnamurti Foundation of America/Oak Grove School (Ojai, CA, 1977-1980 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Kroeger, Mr. and Mrs. Myron/ Kroeger residence(Oakview, CA,1976-1978 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Kubovec, Mr. and Mrs. Russ/Kubovec residence(Ojai, CA,1985 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Kunes, Mr. and Mrs. Robert/Robert Kunes residence(Upper Ojai, CA, 1979 Residence):[Ms]
  - Landis, Charles(Los Angeles, CA,1989):[Ms]
  - Landucci, Evelyn/Wheeler Hot Springs, future development (Ojai, CA, 1988-1989 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Larry Oeth/Oeth Duplex(1985 Residence):[Ms]
  - Larsen, Les/The Bush School/1484 E. Ojai Ave(Ojai, CA,1980 Institutional):[ Ms]
  - Lawewnce, Anthony/Lawrence residence(Ojai, CA, 1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Lazarus, Stan/ Ojai Pharmacy (Ojai, CA, 1979-1981Commercial):[Ms]
  - Leonard, Wayne/ Leonard residence (Ojai, CA, 1990 Residence):[Ms]
  - Lindberg/Lindberg Residence (1986):[Ms]
  - Live Oak Realty/U.S. Forest Service Building (Ojai, CA, 1968 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Lobel/Lobel residence (1983-1984 Residence):[Ms]
  - Louderback, Anthony/Louderback residence(Ojai, CA, 1989 Residence):[Ms]
  - Low, Mr. and Mrs. Don/Low residence (Ojai, CA, 1978 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Lynn Raines/Rain's Realty Company (formerly Rain's Market)(Ojai, CA, 1972 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - MacDonald, Mr. and Mrs. Ken/ MacDonald residence (Ojai, CA, 1976-1977 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Mark Nelson/Nelson residence(Ojai, CA,1989 Residence):[Ms]
  - Martin, Mr. and Mrs. Robert/Martin guest house (Ojai, CA, 1987 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Martin, Robert [or Mr. and Mrs. Hans Schiff] /Lot 33, Tract 1443 Del Oro Subdivision Libbey Ave, Ojai, CA(Ojai, CA, 1988):[Ms,Dr]
  - Mason, David/ Village Florist Shop with office space in Redevelopment area of Ojai (Ojai, CA, 1978-1983 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Matta, Berto/Matta's Ristorante(Woodland Hills, CA, 1984-1986 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - McAllister, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph/McAllister residence (Ojai, CA, 1971 Residence):[Ms]
  - Meditation Groups, Inc./Meditation Mount (Ojai, CA, 1969-1972 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - McPherson, Gary/McPherson residence (Ojai ,CA,1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Michelson, Cleo/Michelson residence(Ojai, CA,1972 Residence):[Ms]
  - Mission Federal Savings and Loan Association/ Mission Federal Savings and Loan in the Maricopa Building (Ojai, CA, 1979 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Moncharsh, Philip and Karen/Moncharsh residence(Ojai,CA, 1989 Residence):[Ms]
  - Moser restaurant (Residence):[Ms]
  - Ocean Services Corp./Fisherman's Quay (San Buenaventura, CA, 1978-1984 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Office of the State Architect/ Department of Motor Vehicles - Arleta, Office Building and Parking Facilities (San Fernando Valley, CA, 1978-1982 Institutional):[Ms,Dr]
  - Ojai (City of)/Ojai Elementary (Ojai, CA, 1976 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Ojai (City of)/Libby Park Activities Building (Ojai, CA, 1989 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ojai (City of)/Ojai Redevelopment Project (Ojai, CA, 1971-1982 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai (City of)/Chamber of Commerce (Ojai, CA, 1981-1982 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Ojai (City of)/ Libbey Park Restrooms(Ojai, CA, 1973; 1986-1987 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ojai (City of)/ Masterplan(Ojai, CA, Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ojai (City of)/ Redevelopment Project -Arcade Redevelopment / Ojai Redevelopment (Ojai, CA,1990 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ojai (City of)/ Ojai Police Facility (Ojai, CA, 1975 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ojai/proposed warehouse on N. Ventura Ave (CA, Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ojai/Signage - Help-U-Sell; Zelma Wilson (CA,Commercial): [Ms,Dr]
  - Ojai Hacienda Center and Administration Center (Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Pet Hospital/Ojai Pet Hospital(Ojai,CA, 1972 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Plaza Building (Ojai, CA,1981 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Realty/ Ojai Realty(Ojai, CA, 1979-1980 Commercial): [Ms]
  - Ojai Unified School District/Ojai Valley Museum (Ojai, CA,1988 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley Inn and Country Club/Ojai Valley News (Ojai, CA, 1987-1994 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley Museum Expansion -- West Kent and Bruce Dunwoody/Ojai Valley News(Ojai, CA, 1989-1992 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley News/(Ojai, CA, 1973-1983 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley News/Ojai Valley Racquet Club, remodel and addition (Ojai, CA,1989 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley Racquet Club/Ojai Valley Racquet Club (Ojai, CA,1975-1981 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley Racquet Club/ Ojai Valley Racquet Club, remodel and addition (Ojai,CA, 1987-1988 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Ojai Valley State Bank/Ojai Valley State Bank (Ojai, CA,1972 Commercial):[Dr]
  - Ojai Valley Tennis Club/ Ojai Valley Tennis Club in Libbey Park (Ojai, CA, 1989 Commercial): [Ms]
  - Ojai Valley Women's Club Inc./(Ojai, CA,1977):[Ms]
  - Olivas,William and Marcia/Matilija Hot Springs Resort (Ojai, CA, 1973-1974 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Owens, William and Ruth/Owens residence( Oak View,CA, 1986-1989 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Paine, Noel and Jim/ Paine residence(Ojai,CA, 1983 Residence):[Ms]
  - Parade float(Commercial):[Dr]
  - Peck, William/ Peck residence (Ventura, CA, 1973-1974 Residence):[Ms]
  - Petersdorf, Mr. and Mrs. Rudolph/Signal Street Property (Ojai, CA, 1979-1980):[Ms, Dr]
  - Pima Developers, Ltd. (Lawrence G. Malanfant); Surfland Development Corporation/ Matilija Plaza (Ojai, CA, 1978-1981 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Pope, Tom and Freya/Pope Residence(Ojai, CA, 1982 Residence):[Ms]
  - Preston, Yvonne/Arcade Place (Korbs Building)(Ojai,CA, 1979-1980 Commercial):[Ms]
  - R.W. McCarthy & Associates/Ojai Valley Business Park(Ojai ,CA, 1982-1985 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Rabieassl, Salman/Rabieassl Commercial Building (Ojai, CA,1981-1985 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Radio Ojai Inc./ Radio Transmitter Station (Ojai, CA, 1971 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Rains, Alan/Rains Department Store (Ojai, CA, 1979 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ramalle, Babo/Aliso & Montgomery/Ramalle residence (1985 Residence):[Ms]
  - Rang, Pat and King/Rang residence(Ojai,CA, 1990 Residence):[Ms]
  - Remedios, Peter/Commercial Building, Hwy. 22(Mira Monte, CA, 1987Residence):[Ms]
  - Remutulah Merali/Nazarene Church (Ojai,CA, 1985 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Residence, 817 Del Oro Dr.(Ojai, CA,Residence):[Ms]
  - Ruch, Jim and Sandy/Commercial property(Ojai, CA,1992 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Running Ridge/Rybarczyk Residence(Ojai,CA ,1977-1981 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Rybarczyk, Mr. and Mrs. Henry/Rybarczyk Residence(Ojai,CA,1968-1969Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Scanlin, Dan; Hans Uei (City of)/Ojai Rancho Motel(City of San Buenaventura, CA,1977Commercial):[Ms]
  - Schlichter, Gary and Cathleen/Schlichter residence, remodel(Ojai, CA, 1982-1983 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Scott, Richard/Richard N. Scott Center(Ojai, CA,1987-1991 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Seelos, Brian/Dream Weaver Expansion(Ojai, CA,1989-1990 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Signal Ave. Associates/Sign designs [includes signage for El Paseo](Ventura,CA,1985 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Silver, Robert and Dorothy/"Ojai Marketplace" building at South-east corner of Matilija and Signal Streets (Ojai, CA,1988 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Simi Valley (City of)/Senior Citizen Center(Ojai,CA,1984-1986 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Single Family residence, near 514 Del Norte Road(Simi Valley,CA,1979-1984 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Sinkinson, M.D., Dr. Craig /Ojai Country Clinic (Ojai, CA, 1978 Residence):[Ms]
  - Smart, Jack and Jean /Smart residence (Ojai, CA,1982-1983 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Smithers, Brett and Christine/Smithers residence (Ojai, CA, 1987-1988 Residence): [ Ms, Dr ]
  - South Coast Area Transit /Maintenance and Operating Facility(Ojai, CA,1987 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Spasiano Restaurant, remodel( Oxnard, CA,1977-1981Institutional):[Ms]
  - Spears, Bob and Nancy/Spears residence (in Rancho Matilija development)(1984 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Speight, Mr. and Mrs. Henry/Speight residence(Ojai, CA, 1981-1992 Residence):[Ms]
  - Spencer, Joan and Frank/Spencer residence (Goleta, CA, 1984-1986 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - St. Thomas Aquinas College/Dorm(Institutional):[Dr]
  - Stroberg, Al and Betsey Patterson/ Stroberg/Patterson residence (Ojai, CA, 1989-1991 Residence): [Ms, Dr]
  - Susan Nahabedian/Art Gallery (Ojai, CA,1990 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Tabor, Dr. and Mrs. Bruce /Tabor residence (Ojai, CA, 1976 Commercial):[Dr]
  - Thatcher, Tony and Aleta Londo/ Friend's Ranch Outdoor Market (Ojai, CA,1976 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - The Thatcher School/Thatcher School, Master Plan (Ojai, CA, 1987-1989 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - The Thacher School/ Thacher School, Basketball Courts (Ojai, CA, 1981 Institutional):[Ms]
  - The Thacher School/Thacher School, Ceramic Studio remodel (Ojai, CA, Institutional):[Ms]
  - The Thacher School/Thacher School, Chickering Stables(Ojai, CA, 1981 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - The Thacher School/ Thacher School, Faculty Residences (Ojai,CA, 1982-1983 Institutional):[Ms,Dr]
  - The Thacher School/Thacher School, Handball Courts (Ojai, CA, 1981 Institutional):[Ms]
  - The Thacher School/ Thacher School, Humanities Building, remodel (Ojai, CA, 1982 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Toth, Bob and Jerrold Fine/Toth-Fine residence (Ojai, CA,1976-1978 Residence):[Ms]
  - Tymstra, Mr. and Mrs. F.T./Tymstra residence (2)(Ojai, CA, 1972 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Tyner, Jim/ El Paseo Business Center Signage [see also Signal Ave. Associates under Client Name](Ojai, CA, commercial): [Ms, Dr]
  - U.S. Naval Construction Battalion Center/ Building 1228 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1981 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - U.S. Naval Construction Battalion Center/ Unaccompanied Enlisted Personnel Housing (UEPH) Building 56-60 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1978-1986 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/Building 240 & 248 (Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Ventura/Unitarian Universalist Church of Ventura (Ventura, CA, 1985-1987 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Venture County/ Terry House(CA,Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/ Child Care Center (Oak Harbor, WA, Institutional):[Dr]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/BOQ, Building 170 (Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1983 Institutional):[Ms]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/ Building 246 (Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/Building 356 (Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1986 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/ Building 445(Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/Building 553 (Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1986 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - United States Navy, Naval Air Station/ Building 761(Point Mugu, CA, 1982-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Unknown/ Unidentified compund-has Brother's quarters(n.d.):[Dr]
  - Vanderhoef/ Vanderhoef & Cunningham Redidence (Residence):[Ms]
  - Ventura (County of)/Colston Youth Center remodeling (CA, 1979-1981 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Ventura (County of)/Creek Road Bridges (Ventura Co., CA, Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ventura County (County of)/Creek Road Bridges No.314 (Ventura Co., CA, Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ventura (County of)/Juvenille Hall, addition (San Buenaventura, CA, 1953 Institutional): Roy C. Wilson, Architect:[Dr]
  - Ventura (County of)/Oak View Community Center(Oak View, CA, 1978-1981 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ventura (County of)/ Simi Valley Library (Simi Valley, CA, 1976-1980 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ventura (County of)/ Tatum Center Sleeping Rooms Remodel, Ventura Co. Hospital (Ventura, CA, 1979-1981 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ventura County Sheriff Office/ Honor Farm Interim Detention Facility (Ventura Co., CA, 1976 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Ventura County Sheriff Office/ Slaughter House Branch Jail Honor Farm (Ventura Co., CA, 1984-1986 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Ventura County Star Free Press/(Ventura, CA, 1977 commercial):Donald R. Goss Associates Newsplant Design Planning San Angelo, TX; Rasmussen, Love & Ellinwood Architecture Ventura, CA (architects):[Ms]
  - Ventura Public Works Agency/ Ojai Village Commerical Center (Ojai, CA,1989 commercial):[Ms]
  - Vernazza, J. Ben/Robo Car Wash (Ojai, CA, 1971 commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Villanova Preparatory School/ William P. Clark Gymnasium (Ojai, CA,1986-1991Institutional):[Ms]
  - Volz, Fred/Volz residence(Ojai, CA, 1985 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Vrabec, Dale and Sylvia/ Vrabec residence (Ojai, CA, 1974-1975 Residence):[Ms]
  - Wann, Arthur and Anita/ Office and commercial building (Meiners Oaks, CA, 1977-1978 commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Weirich [Weyrich], Wayne and James Bernier/Office Building (N. Ventura, Ojai, CA,commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - West, Allan and Joyce/West residence(Ojai, CA, 1990-1993 Residence):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 1219 ( Port Hueneme, CA, 1982-1983 Institutional): [Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 1230 ( Port Hueneme,CA, 1982 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/Building 1362 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1981-1983 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 445 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1982 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/Building 447-1(Port Hueneme, CA,1981-1982 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/Building 452 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1981-1982 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/Building 452 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1981-1982 Institutional ): [ Ms ]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 5 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1982-1984 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command /Building 511 ( Port Hueneme, CA, 1981-1982 Institutional): [Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 58 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1982-1983 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 61 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1981-1985 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Building 850 (Port Hueneme, CA, 1978-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Child Care Center, Naval Construction Battalion Center (Port Hueneme, CA,1978-1986 Institutional):[Ms,Dr]
  - Western Division Naval Facilities Engineering Command/ Port Hueneme Buildings (Port Hueneme, CA, 1982-1983 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Westrom, Margaret and Duane/Westrom residence, remodel (Ojai, CA, 1988-1989 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Whitmeyer, Russ/Whitmeyer residence, remodel (1980 Residence):[Ms]
  - Will, Ted/ Retirement Care Facility (1989 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Willner George/ Willner Residence, remodeling and landscaping (Ojai, CA, 1973-1974 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Willsrud/ Residence (Ojai, CA, Residence):[Ms]
  - Willsrud, Thor/Willsrud residence (Ojai, CA, 1984-1985 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Wilson, Zelma/ Zelma's office design (Commercial):[Dr]
  - Wise, Mr. and Mrs. J.(Ojai, CA, 1989 Residence):[Ms]
  - World University/ World University, Dormitory and Classrooms (Ojai, CA, 1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Youth Employment Service, proposed offices at Ojai Elementary School (Ojai, CA, Institutional):[Ms]
  - Zeiger, Irving( Los Angeles, CA, 1958):Robert Kennard, Architect:[Dr]
  - Zinsmeir, David/ Commander Cornball Ice Cream Shop, new awning (Ojai, CA, 1985 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Zrabec/Zrabec Residence (Ojai, CA, Residence):[Dr]